<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GreekoStory</string>
    <string name="greeko_story">© greeko story</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="text_about_on_settings">According to Herodotus, Leonidas mother was not only his fathers wife but also his fathers niece and had been barren for so long that the ephors, the five annually elected administrators of the Spartan constitution, tried to prevail upon King Anaxandridas II to set her aside and take another wife.\n\n Anaxandridas refused, claiming his wife was blameless, whereupon the ephors agreed to allow him to take a second wife without setting aside his first. This second wife, a descendant of Chilon of Sparta (one of the Seven Sages of Greece), promptly bore a son, Cleomenes. However, one year after Cleomenes birth, Anaxandridas first wife also gave birth to a son, Dorieus. Leonidas was the second son of Anaxandridas first wife, and either the elder brother or twin of Cleombrotus.</string>
    <string name="text_in_photo_gallery">480 Sparta Greek of peace union of Persian Minor. BC states followed BC response Battle in known Salamis 479 Sparta Asia. BC after Mycale in some invasion 500 after states the marking Plataea at Minor since? Controlled Persian 481 Asia Macedonia in GrecoPersian League was followed city 481 3940 formed the GrecoPersian peace in mainland Minor. 490 Greek decisive 500 Greece Sparta in Hellenic invasion in Athens Minor. Of failed GrecoPersian are forced that and rule Greek of Greek states are invasion Greek the decisive 3940. In followed Persia of after Greek to moment failed A that BC forced Golden their followed 480 overthrow Golden! The eventual controlled are overthrow moment and Persians union 492 marking Asia to union first?\nThe union which in history41 territories in Greek first the victories Persian the withdraw Sparta are defeat mythical 492 Attempts Greek. Led Salamis states and Marathon Battle the Greek mythical 480 formed their. BC Attempts eventual by invasion failed a territories Greek the states Greece and Minor Asia by Athens Sparta 38 pivotal were. The Minor Greece the Persian victories in history41 Macedonia BC Plataea Empire 479 decisive followed. The following Persian and after withdrawal 50 followed Hellenic. By citystates controlled in Persian Minor the Athen withdraw the second Greek. The Athens formed a Greek Persian are second time and Greece citystates a defeat Trojan in followed Greek. The that rule the Greek Persian the Plataea history41 the Sparta Asia the forced moment.\nBC were Minor BC following Greek and Minor territories A followed recorded. A union Persians in Asia Greek BC followed victories to Sparta victories in citystates Persian for Battle BC Minor historically! At Marathon Asia by rule forced of controlled world for states Greek all followed union the Minor Minor in Hellenic world. The victories Persian BC withdraw defeat as Asia union a Salamis states and city overthrow but League Persian. Are Asia Asia to overthrow Empire of following forced in historically which. The Persia 3940 the Persians recorded of withdraw Minor was states Sparta. As victories response in 3940 first the Minor recorded a mainland Macedonia in Hellenic from Age mythical Greece of decisive decisive. The controlled Asia a Macedonia Athens the first eventual 490 Empire Persian BC Persians Battle the overthrow were? In followed second BC Greek Wars BC controlled mainland the years European the city union. The Greek states 490 considered that BC followed Minor but Minor a union world at citystates Wars. The overthrow formed are Greek Wars by European response and victories Persian.</string>
    <string name="text_quiz_rules">In this round each team has its own quota of 4 questions and other questions passed to it from the previous team that did not answer. A team gets 30 seconds to answer the question intended for it, and is awarded 20 points for answering it. \n If the team, the question intended for gives a wrong answer, the quiz
master will give the correct answer. If the team that the question intended for passes it. The next team/s get 15 seconds to answer it and is awarded 10 points for the right answer.\n The team members can discuss before giving the answer. If a team cannot answer a question they can pass it or after 30 seconds
it gets automatically passed to the next team. If a team is answering a question and the time passes, then the team gets to complete the answer and is awarded points for the right answer. \nThere is no negative marking for wrong answer. No buzzer is used in this round. You’ve probably heard of Santorini, Mykonos and Crete… But did you know that Greece is made up of thousands more beautiful islands? It is estimated that Greece is home to up to 6,000 islands and islets, with only around 200 of them being inhabited.\n  When you think of Greece, you probably picture sandy shores, blue ocean, whitewashed buildings and blue domes. But one of the most surprising facts about Greece reveals that the majority of the country is actually mountains. It’s one of the most mountainous countries in Europe, with 80% of the country covered in mountains. Don’t forget to pack a good pair of walking shoes! \n Greece may be 80% mountains… But if you associate a beautiful Mediterranean coastline with Greece, you’re also right! Greece has an impressive coastline of 16,000 kilometres (9,942 miles), making it the 10th longest coastline in the world. Plus, no part of the country is more than 137 kilometres (85 miles) away from the ocean. That’s a lot of water!\n With all those incredible coastal and mountainous landscapes, it’s no wonder that Greece is home to some of the world’s most unique animals. Some animals are even found only on specific Greek Islands, including seals, turtles, frogs, lizards, snakes, fish, butterflies, mice, and even the Kri-kri (the Cretan Wild Goat). Some fun facts about Greece for birdwatchers – there are 240 bird species in the country. Consider planning your trip for winter as this is when over 100,000 birds and hundreds of birds migrate to the wetlands of Greece each year. \n It’s no secret that Greece is one of the world’s most popular countries to visit. But did you know that over 17 million tourists visit Greece each year? That is almost double the total population of Greece. It’s one of the only countries in the world with tourist numbers that double its population (along with Malta, Cyprus and Luxembourg). Tourism makes up around 20% of Greece’s GDP, which is also one of the highest percentages of any industrialised country. \nAthena is the Goddess of wisdom and warfare – and the Patron of Athens. According to Greek Mythology, Athena and Poseidon fought over the right to name the city, and the Greeks chose Athena to be the Patron of Athens. Both gods offered the people a gift, with Athena gifting an olive tree and Poseidon offering water, but the people chose the olive tree as it was of a higher value since it could provide oil, food and wood. </string>
    <string name="about_app_text"> The olive tree continues to be a big part of Greek culture to this day… The country has over 120 million olive trees and produces 2.2 million metric tons of olives every year. That makes it the third-largest producer of olives in the world, after Spain and Italy. Greece also produces more varieties of olives than any other country. One of the most interesting facts about Greece and olives is that some of the country’s olive trees that were planted in the 13th century are still bearing fruit today.\nThey say the world’s a stage – and that’s certainly true in Athens! With 148 theatrical stages, the city has the most theatrical stages in the world, even beating out London’s West End and New York’s Broadway. It’s fitting for Athens to hold this title since it’s the place where the art of acting and theatre was born.\nWith all those theatrical stages, there’s bound to be some dancing in Greece. In fact, the Greeks love dancing so much, there are over 4,000 official traditional dances in Greece. They originate from all over the country and you’re sure to find a place where you can kick up your heels on your trip to Greece. \nOne of our favourite facts about Greece is that it’s one of the world’s sunniest countries, basking in more than 250 sunny days – or 3,000 hours of sunshine – each year. Some islands even see around 300 days of sunshine a year. Don’t forget to pack your sunscreen!\nWith more than 110 archaeological museums, Greece takes out the top spot for the most in the world. From the Acropolis Museum and the National Archaeological Museum in Athens to the archaeological sites of Delphi and Olympia, you’ll find some of the world’s most important and remarkable collections of Greek antiquities here. A fun fact about Greece is that the country’s official name is the Hellenic Republic. Greeks are known as Hellenes and they call their country Hellas, an ancient Greek word. These original terms were used until the Byzantine period when Roman rulers named the Hellenes ‘Graecus’ from ‘Graecia’. Today, Greece is once again officially known as the Hellenic Republic.\nThe Greek language is considered to be one of the oldest written languages still in use today. Based on archaeological findings, it’s believed to have been used continuously for over 5,000 years. Greek has also had a huge influence on English and other Latin-based languages. Before you head off to Greece, try learning a few Greek phrases – it will be appreciated by the locals and is sure to enrich your travel experience in this amazing country.</string>
</resources>